entergy.com 2019-11-25

# Entergy - Privacy Policy | Entergy | We Power Life

**Entergy Corporation and Affiliates**

**Privacy Policy**

Entergy Corporation is a holding company for individual public utility companies, among other affiliates. Each of these public utility companies and other affiliates is a separate and distinct legal entity. Each public utility subsidiary of Entergy Corporation has its own service territory, federal and/or state utility regulatory regime(s), rate structure(s), and customers. Neither Entergy Corporation nor any subsidiary or other affiliate of Entergy Corporation shall be liable for the obligations, or entitled to the benefits of, any other subsidiary or affiliate of Entergy Corporation, except as may be expressly provided by a duly authorized and executed, legally enforceable written agreement. The public utility subsidiaries of Entergy Corporation that provide retail electric and/or gas utility services are the following:

  * Entergy Arkansas, LLC
  * Entergy Louisiana, LLC
  * Entergy Mississippi, LLC
  * Entergy New Orleans, LLC
  * Entergy Texas, Inc.

Solely for reasons of convenience, the term “Entergy” is used herein to refer individually and collectively to Entergy Corporation and its affiliates, including, but not limited to, the public utility companies named above.

Entergy’s postal address is:

P.O. Box 61000  
L-ENT-6H  
New Orleans, LA 70161  
Attention: Web Communications Manager

Entergy can also be reached via email by [clicking here](https://secure.entergy.com/forms/Simple.aspx?FormId=232&RegionId=CORP).

The term “Website” refers to this Entergy website, and the term “Web Services” refers to any and all services of any kind available through this Website, including but not limited to account access services, paperless bill delivery services, and one-time and repetitive bill payment services. You can learn more about the terms, conditions, and policies for the use of the Website and Web Services by clicking here.

We understand how important privacy is to you. We hope this Privacy Policy will answer your privacy questions.

**1\. Privacy Commitment**

Entergy may collect different information about you in different situations, which are described in more detail below.  This information may include your name along with one or more of the following: address, email address, phone number, fax number, tax identification number, IP address, social security number, resume, bank name and account number, credit card number and billing details, credit card provider, Entergy utility account number, User or other password, or other information that might identify you (“Personal Information”).   

Except as expressly provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personal Information with other organizations for their commercial or marketing purposes, nor will we intentionally disclose your Personal Information to third parties.

As a general matter, we may disclose Personal Information:

  * when authorized by you or when necessary to provide a service you have requested;
  * to communicate with you about issues related to your application, account, or request for service;
  * when necessary to comply with an order of a government agency or court, when requested by a government regulator, or as otherwise required by law, or requested in writing by law enforcement;
  * to investigate and address system problems and to protect the security of the Website; or
  * to a purchaser in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer of all or part of our business or company.

Additionally, we may disclose your Personal Information to individual contractors and third-party service providers who assist us in providing you with services, or with other permitted uses of your Personal Information (subject to appropriate confidentiality agreements).  

The following sections describe in more detail the data we collect and how we use that data.

**2\. Information We Collect Automatically**

We may collect all information about all interactions between your web browser and the Entergy Website and other websites unrelated to Entergy that you visit, including your IP address, the web pages you visit, how long you visit them and what you do while visiting them.  For example, we may collect information that tells us how long you spent on a certain page, what information you supplied, or what boxes you did or did not check.  Web browsers may provide a large amount of information that we may also collect, including your time zone, browser type and version, language preference, and any cookies that we have set (see below for an explanation of cookies).  

We may use this information for a number of purposes including revising our web pages to make them more user-friendly, diagnosing problems, investigating security issues, supporting our training efforts, or documenting your interaction with the Website or other websites, and for marketing purposes. This information is also used in the aggregate in order to evaluate our Website’s effectiveness and to improve performance, and for marketing purposes.

Your device’s location services may be used to provide an improved experience when showing information relevant to your location, to advise us about potential outages that you may report, or to provide important information relevant to you. Location information is optional, and may be shared with third parties who provide services to us.  If you decline the location services through your device’s operating system, your location will not be used and any service, such as Entergy’s outage maps, may default to alternative methods of helping you find information relevant to your location.

Privacy Policies for third-party services we use to collect user data on our mobile app are linked below: 

Some parts of this Website use cookies.  Our Website may ask your web browser to store automatically a small text file on your computer, which will then be sent back to our Website each time you click on a new page on our Website. This enables us to provide you with the best experience possible. A cookie cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer by adjusting your web browser privacy settings or by other widely available methods.  Note that you may not be able to use certain features of this Website if your web browser does not accept cookies, or your privacy settings prevent certain access.

**3\. Information We Collect from All Users**

In connection with your use of the Web Services, we may collect your name, addresses, telephone number, and email address. For members of the general public, we may collect this information in the course of completing surveys, service eligibility determination, inquiries, and site registration. Other users of the Website may provide this information in connection with Web Services described in more detail below.

We may use this information to provide the requested service, notify you about updates or changes to our Website, alert you when new services, options, products, or features become available, and to offer you the opportunity to donate to Entergy’s charitable funds, such as the Power to Care Fund.

**4\. Information We Collect from Entergy Customers**

When you initiate service with Entergy, regardless of whether you do so using this Website, over the phone, through our walk-in customer care centers, via fax, or by email, we will collect certain information that may include certain Personal Information.  

We will use this information for activities including:

• to identify you in connection with establishing an account;  
• to establish a deposit amount (if any);  
• to maintain your account;  
• to process, evaluate, and respond to account and service requests, inquiries and applications you make as a Customer;  
• to provide online bills or usage information;  
• to collect amounts due on your account;  
• to close the account;    
• to provide, administer, and communicate with you about products and services;  
• to operate, evaluate, and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; performing market research; managing our advertising and marketing; analyzing our products, services, and Websites; administering our Websites; and performing accounting, auditing, reconciliation, and collection activities);    
• to protect against and prevent fraud, unauthorized activity, claims, and other liabilities; and  
• to comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, industry standards, and our policies and terms of use.

We may engage third parties to assist us in providing you with service.  For example, we may:

• send certain Personal Information to a credit-reporting agency to help us determine a deposit amount;  
• allow an IT service provider to access Personal Information in order to provide us with technology-related customer service issues; or  
• provide collection agents with Personal Information in connection with collecting amounts due on an account.

**5\. Information We Collect From Job Applicants**

As a job applicant, we will collect the information that we need to evaluate your application, such as your resume and job application information.   

We endeavor not to disclose information contained in resumes or job applications (which may include Personal Information) to third parties, except as provided below. We endeavor to limit internal access to resumes and job applications to those individuals who need to know this information.

We will use the information you provide as necessary to evaluate your job application. In connection with your job application, we may provide your information to third parties (subject to appropriate confidentiality agreements), including for the purpose of administering and processing your application, and performing background checks and drug screenings.

You may choose to provide information on your gender, race, or ethnicity on a voluntary basis. We will not consider either this information, or your choice to decline to provide it, in evaluating your qualifications for employment with us.  If you provide such information, we may use it to the extent necessary or appropriate for compliance with relevant legal or contractual obligations, and for other internal purposes.

**6\. Information We Collect From Vendors and Potential Vendors**

As a vendor or potential vendor to Entergy, we will collect the information that we need, including Personal Information, to process your application to become a vendor to Entergy. For example, we may use this information to conduct background checks and drug screenings. We may also use it to evaluate your work and proposals to work, process payments, comply with reporting obligations, and for other internal business purposes. In addition to Personal information, we may also collect information on you that we need to comply with Entergy’s federal reporting requirements concerning its expenditures with small, small-disadvantaged, minority-, and women-owned businesses.

**7\. Information We Collect From Third Parties**

We collect information supplied to this Website by third parties, e.g. information submitted by non-profits in connection with certain home energy assistance programs. This information includes your name, account number, and payment information needed to process pledges made by third-parties in connection with your account.

**8\. Personal Information Provided in Connection with the Web Services and other Entergy services**

In connection with your use of Web Services, you may be asked to create an account, and to provide a password.  You shall be responsible for the use, security, and safety of such account and password.

**9\. Email Addresses, Postal Mail Addresses, and Phone Numbers**

Individuals who supply their addresses (email or postal mail) or phone numbers (land-line or cell) may receive periodic messages from Entergy with information on new products and services, upcoming events or news that may be of interest, account-related information, information about your job or vendor application, information on your job-related activities (if employed by Entergy), or opportunities to donate to Entergy’s charitable funds such as the Power to Care Fund.  If you do not want to receive such communications from Entergy in the future (except with respect to communications in connection with your Entergy account, your request for service, your job or vendor application, or your job-related activities, if employed by Entergy), please let us know by [clicking here](https://secure.entergy.com/forms/Simple.aspx?FormId=229&RegionId=CORP) and telling us that you do not want to receive these types of communications. We will comply with such requests as required by law, or requested in writing by law enforcement.

**10\. Unsolicited Material Not Confidential**

Unless provided by you in connection with the Web Services or other Entergy service, in connection with your application for a job, your employment with Entergy, your vendor application, or unless Entergy specifically notes otherwise, any Personal Information or any other information or material sent to us on an unsolicited basis will be deemed NOT to be confidential.

**11\. Submissions to Entergy**

Any information, suggestion, idea, graphic, remark, or other submission made by a user to Entergy through this Website or in connection with the accessing of the Web Services whether submitted by email or otherwise, shall become the exclusive property of Entergy, and shall not be deemed to be confidential, except as provided by this Privacy Policy. Entergy shall be entitled to use any such submission and any derivative works created therefrom, and any related concepts, ideas, techniques, or know-how for any lawful purpose without any obligation to any user submitting the same and without any other restriction, permission, or compensation. Each user making any such submission thereby acknowledges the originality of such submission and accepts responsibility for its accuracy, completeness, appropriateness, and legality.

**12\. Data Security**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

**13.  Online Advertising**

On our Websites, we may collect information about your online activities to provide advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests.  You can choose whether to have your information collected for this purpose. This section of our Privacy Policy provides details and explains how to exercise your choices.

You may see certain ads on other Websites because we participate in advertising networks. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographic, behavioral and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs, and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests.  The information our ad network vendors collect includes information about your visits to Websites that participate in the vendors’ advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the Websites. This data collection and ad-targeting takes place both on our Websites and on third-party Websites that participate in the ad networks, such as Websites that feature advertisements delivered by the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.  You can learn how to opt-out of third-party vendors’ use of cookies at Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

**14\. Links to Other Websites**

Our Websites may contain links to other sites for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by companies not affiliated with us.  Linked sites may have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit them.  We are not responsible for the content of any sites that are not affiliated with us, any use of those sites, or the privacy practices of those sites.  

**15\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This privacy notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will include the date on which this privacy policy was last updated.  Prior versions of this Privacy Policy are available. Please contact us at the address above.

_Last Updated:  August 6, 2019_
